export const backend = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What is Node.js?',
        options: [
          'A front-end JavaScript library',
          'A runtime for executing JavaScript code server-side',
          'A relational database management system',
          'A markup language for building web pages',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'A runtime for executing JavaScript code server-side',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Which module in Node.js is used for building web servers?',
        options: ['fs', 'http', 'path', 'net'],
        correctAnswer: 'http',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What does Express.js provide for Node.js development?',
        options: [
          'A templating engine',
          'Middleware to handle HTTP requests and responses',
          'Database management',
          'Authentication services',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Middleware to handle HTTP requests and responses',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'How can you install external packages in a Node.js project?',
        options: [
          'Using npm (Node Package Manager)',
          'By directly downloading the source code',
          'Using a package manager unrelated to Node.js',
          'By copying and pasting the code into the project',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Using npm (Node Package Manager)',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What is the purpose of the Express method "app.use()"?',
        options: [
          'To define a new route',
          'To configure middleware for the application',
          'To set up a static file server',
          'To define a template engine',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'To configure middleware for the application',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'Which HTTP method is used for updating data on the server in a RESTful API?',
        options: ['GET', 'POST', 'PUT', 'DELETE'],
        correctAnswer: 'PUT',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What does the acronym API stand for in the context of web development?',
        options: [
          'Advanced Programming Interface',
          'Application Programming Interface',
          'Automated Programming Interface',
          'All Programming Interface',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What is middleware in the context of Express.js?',
        options: [
          'A JavaScript framework for building web applications',
          'Software that runs on the client side',
          'Functions that have access to the request and response objects',
          'A data storage system',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Functions that have access to the request and response objects',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is npm?',
        options: [
          'Node Package Manager',
          'Node Project Manager',
          'New Project Maker',
          'Node Package Module',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Node Package Manager',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Which module is used for working with file paths in Node.js?',
        options: ['fs', 'path', 'http', 'url'],
        correctAnswer: 'path',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
]